♪♪♪
[engine turns off]
You're wasting time with me.
You should be looking
for those hooligans
he had hanging around.
Mr. Liu.
He owns the building
that has the import export
business on the first floor.
Patrick Jane
I rented him the upstairs
because he seemed reliable.
But he wasn't.
You find those kids.
I don't need
these kind of problems.
What are you
so scared about?
Scared about losing money,
that's what.
Mm.
I need to get back to work.
Me, too.
[camera shutter clicks]
[Patrick]
'Morning, Lisbon.'
'What do we have here?'
[Lisbon]
'Somebody named Theissens.'
He doesn't have a wallet on him,
but I'm not thinking robbery.
Looks like
a puritan tailor shop.
Helpful. That's it?
That's all you're gonna say?
Till I think of something
useful to say, yes.
No murder weapon, but there was
this... in his mouth.
In his mouth?
This is definitely not
a robbery.
- Crime of passion?
- Or a message.
Let's keep the feather
out of any public statements.
It could be useful
identifying the killer.
A feather?
Now we're getting somewhere.
Find out
where this came from.
Came from his mouth.
Yes, uh, before
it was in his... mouth.
Maybe the killer brought it in?
Or the killers?
Could be
this is gang-related.
A golden feather?
It's a little camp for
gangsters, don't you think?
I think it has
something to do with dresses.
Dresses..
Hmm.
Interesting.
[click]
Ah, secret room.
[door bangs]
Ooh-la-la!
Et voila!
The murder weapon.
[theme music
[telephone ringing]
So Wyck Theissens was a clothing
designer in New York and Paris.
Real high-end stuff.
Cutting edge. Very successful.
Then about three years ago,
it all went bad.
Bad how?
Bad like this.
You're... you're not taping
this, are you?
[Man]
'No. We're just warming up.'
'Uh, the fashion world is...'
'Yeah, uh, the fashion world'
'is pond scum and monsters.
That's all it is. They're...'
'It's crawling lickspittle
pond scum like you, and...'
'warty, great monsters
like Guy Duval.'
Who's Duval?
He's a French C.E.O.
Of a luxury goods conglomerate.
Holdings are mostly jewelry,
watches, perfume, fashion.
He was backing Theissens'
clothing line, but obviously,
he fired him
after that video came out.
And I'm part of it all.
Look at me.
What an ugly creep I am.
[glass shatters]
That's about two years ago.
Theissens had a breakdown
and disappeared.
What was he doing here?
Not much, according
to the paperwork I got.
Cobbled together
bits of tailoring
for clothing shops around town.
That's it.
What about the stuff
Jane found?
I don't know.
The materials for these dresses
alone comes to $250,000.
- Really?
- Yeah.
Cashmere? Watered silk?
Vicuna?
You know what this stuff
prices out per yard?
What about the murder weapon?
We get prints?
Yeah, but nothing
that matches anything
in the criminal database
or D.M.V.
Look into his financials,
see if you can find anything.
Yeah, you got it.
What?
Fashion? Really?
Come on. Beautiful women
in nice clothes?
What's not to like?
Who would wanna murder
a washed-up fashion designer?
Hmm.
Why would
a washed-up fashion designer
hide a quarter-million dollars
in couture dresses
in a loft in Oakland?
Boss, uh, one of the cops from
the crime scene just called in.
Some kids showed up at the loft,
said they worked for Theissens.
- Have the cops bring them in.
- Will do.
No. Let's go to them.
Seeing them in their own element
will be more revealing.
- You just like the loft.
- I do. It's very nice.
- I've to be back after lunch.
- Oh?
Management meeting.
That Wainwright has too much
time on his hands.
Agent Wainwright?
Patrick Jane
Hi, yeah. I just wanted
to let you know
that Agent Lisbon is needed
urgently in the field
and as important
as your seminar is
she's not gonna be able
to attend.
Okay. Thank you. Bye-bye.
He said it's fine.
See? Simple as that.
Mm. Thanks.
Did it ever occur to you
that I might actually
want to go to the meeting?
No, it didn't. Do you?
No. But it's the principle.
Sorry about that.
So, you were saying?
I wanted to let you know
as a courtesy
I'm still working
the Panzer murder.
The San Joaquin killer case
was solved.
James Panzer was killed
by Tom Maier
the father
of the first victim.
I'm not certain about that.
Well, there was
conclusive evidence.
There was the murder weapon
Panzer's blood
on Maier's clothing
not to mention
the confession Maier wrote
before killing himself.
Right. Odd, don't you think?
Why'd he go to such lengths
to make it look like
Red John was the killer?
It doesn't make any sense.
And why would he send CBI
a video of me?
Who can fathom the mind
of a desperate man?
I'm gonna need all the
department files on Red John.
Of course.
Yeah, whatever
the bureau needs
we are always happy
to be of assistance.
Where were you three
last night?
- Jail.
- Why?
We were at the occupied
demonstration downtown.
Cops said we had to clear the
plaza, then arrested everybody.
We didn't get out
until about an hour ago.
What's your connection
to Wyck Theissens?
We were working with him
on his next collection.
He found us
at the fashion institute.
He wanted to work with people
that were not yet tainted
by the industry.
Yeah. Yeah, that's right.
I mean, he'd been screwed over
once before.
Wasn't gonna make
that mistake again.
Everybody wanted to know
what he was doing..
calling, nosing around.
That why he built
the secret room?
So no one could see the clothes?
Where'd the money come from
for all this?
We made dresses
for the guy downstairs
for him to send back to Asia.
Knockoffs of haute couture.
Mr. Liu?
With the import-export business?
Yeah. It was good training.
Sure. Okay. Any idea why Mr. Liu
would name you three
as the most likely suspects?
[chuckles]
No.
He's just pissed
'cause we weren't gonna
make any more knockoffs
for him.
Yeah, once the collection
was finished
Wyck told him
that we were done.
And when were you gonna
show this collection?
Next week.
Everyone in the fashion world
was coming out for it.
And Theissens
was okay with that?
He didn't have
any bad feelings?
He made his peace with
the business aspects, you know?
Said it was a necessary evil.
Said if you wanna get
your vision to the world..
...you gotta work
with the devil.
Even Guy Duval.
What about Guy Duval?
He's this big
corporate fashion guy.
And, um, two nights ago
after this dinner
at a hotel in San Francisco
Wyck and him were, like,
hugely arguing.
[cell phone rings]
- Hey, boss. What's up?
- I need you to talk to Liu
about paying Theissens
to knock off couture dresses
for the Asian market.
Liu? He's not there?
[Lisbon]
'I'm just leaving his warehouse
now and his employees said'
that he went to speak to you
at the CBI.
Well, somebody's lying.
He's not here.
'Alright.
We need to find Liu.'
We're headed to talk
to Duval now. Keep in touch.
Okay. Will do.
I'm Mr. Duval's assistant.
Can I help you?
Yes, I need to speak with your
boss. It's police business.
I'm sorry. Mr. Duval
is not available at the moment.
When will he be available?
[assistant]
'Let me set something up.
When's a good time for you?'
[cell phone rings]
Would you excuse me?
What's up?
[Rigsby]
'Hey, boss. Just got off
the phone with Oakland P.D.
- Liu's in the wind.
- Already? How?
Cops went to his residence.
Liu was already gone.
Neighbors say three Asian guys
came and he left with them.
Did we get a license plate?
No, but we're working
on his phone now.
Alright. Keep in touch.
Jane and I are
headed back there now.
Could you tell your boss
to call me as soon as possible?
[Lisbon]
'Jane, where are you?'
'Jane?'
'Jane! Where are you?'
[dance music playing]
Next.
Guy Duval, yes?
GheeDuval.
Ah.
The room is closed
to the public.
Mr. Duval, I am so,
so sorry.
Agent Lisbon,
meet GheeDuval.
Hey, Vato,
who invited you to sit?
- And you are?
- I'm Junior Acosta.
I sense that's supposed
to mean something to me.
Junior Acosta's
a very important man.
He puts together
all my shows and parties.
What is this about?
I'm Agent Lisbon
with the CBI
and this is my colleague,
Patrick Jane
We need to ask you some
questions about Wyck Theissens.
What about him?
Theissens is dead.
Oh, my God.
What were you two arguing about
at dinner the other night?
'Was it about
his new clothing line?'
I haven't even seen the line.
He wouldn't let anyone see it.
You're about to buy
a line of clothing
you hadn't been allowed
to see?
He's a genius.
You make allowances.
Was he killed?
Stabbed.
That's ugly.
Yes. Did you make allowances
two years ago
when he called you a monster?
Of course.
I took it as a compliment.
I hope I'm a great monster.
Wyck's career
was derailed by Wyck.
Nobody else.
Where were you last night,
Mr. Duval?
Au lit..
...avec ma femme.
I think that means
he was in bed with his wife.
You released Theissens' video,
didn't you?
Yeah? So? It was news.
So you're responsible
for derailing his career.
No. The truth
is what it is.
I was just a conduit.
Yes. A conduit
is what you are.
Why do keep
a conniving backstabber around?
You think you can
really trust him?
You better watch
your mouth, okay?
Or else what? You gonna gossip
about me behind my back?
I'll show you
what I can do, bitch.
- Oh, okay.
- Put the knife down.
Keep your hands
where I can see 'em.
[clatters]
You fashion people...
You're a very, uh..
passionate lot,
aren't you?
These are all the Red John
case files?
Yes, sir. Four boxes
of physical evidence
plus two hard drives
containing all photographic
and documentary evidence.
Okay, good. Um...
Sign here.
FBI just called me.
They have somebody en route
coming to pick this up.
But one more thing..
Listen to me very closely.
This is
a highly sensitive issue.
You're not to talk
to anybody about this.
Do you understand?
No one.
Yes, sir.
Whatever you say.
Okay, good. If somebody comes
looking for the files
or asks where they've gone
you're to inform me
immediately.
I cannot stress enough
the importance
that this remain secret.
[knock on door]
J.D.!, Who let you
out of the basement?
Hey to you, Agent Lisbon.
- How you been?
- Alright. How 'bout you?
Okay, that's enough.
Thank you. Back to work.
See ya.
Did I call for you?
I just wanted to apologize
for earlier..
Jane calling to get me out
of the management meeting.
Would it be too much to ask you
to schedule a meeting properly?
I'm so sorry.
I didn't realize.
How's your case going?
It's progressing.
We're gonna interview a suspect
if you'd like to sit in.
Unless you're busy.
Paperwork.
The bane of management.
I'd like you to catch me up
when you have the time.
Of course.
Whenever you want.
Um..
How about 45 minutes
in the bullpen?
Yes, sir.
This is a mistake. I got a
little carried away. That's all.
You threatened my colleague
with a knife.
Mm. And you're also a suspect
in Wyck Theissens' murder.
Me? [chuckles]
Why would I kill him?
Well, you ruined Theissens' life
by releasing that video.
It's only natural that he'd
like to return the favor.
Wh-what are you
talking about?
I'm talking about the fact
that Duval wouldn't be happy
to know what you and his wife
are doing behind his back.
What?
If Theissens learned that
you were cuckolding Duval
then, uh, he has every reason
to reveal that fact
which gives you
every reason to kill him.
You can't say anything
about me and Jacqueline.
If Duval found out,
I'd be done.
I'd never work again.
Where were you last night,
Mr. Acosta?
I was at the hotel.
Is there anybody
who can verify that?
Okay, listen..
...if I tell you something..
...you wouldn't let anybody know
it was me that told you, right?
- No.
- It depends on what it is.
Well, I wouldn't.
She might.
Okay, well, the thing is
Wyck and Duval did argue
at dinner the other night.
I heard them.
It was about Tony.
Who's Tony?
Tony Redgrave. He's a photog.
Everybody uses him,
but he's kind of a creep.
Hmm.
The thing is,
everybody uses him.
So you can't say
I told you.
I can't afford
to piss him off, alright?
What were they talking about?
Wyck had brought in
some kids
and he was pissed
that Tony was there.
Oh, he was worried that tony
might get creepy with the kids?
You know, Tony--
he likes 'em young,
you know?
Got it.
- Thank you.
- Got it.
- So we go talk to Tony?
- Take somebody with you.
You're not coming? This could be
your ticket out of this job.
Ha! Wainright's coming in.
He wants to check on things.
More managing? I mean, what--
I-- Someone's gotta do it.
So can we bring me up to date
on the Theissens case?
Well, sir, the alibi for
Theissens' assistants hold up.
They were booked
and held overnight.
But the landlord, Liu--
the one that was selling
Theissens' knockoffs--
he disappeared in a hurry.
And we got a court order
to track his phone.
I can make a call, get this at
the top of their list.
If he had a smartphone,
we might be able to
get an exact location
on the GPS.
- Ifhe had his phone on him.
- Well, let's hope.
And we're also looking
into Guy Duval.
Duval was facing
a shareholder revolt.
He had a lot pinned on making
this Theissens deal go through.
- So if Theissens backed out--
- Then Duval would look weak
and that would make
his position look vulnerable.
And he'd do anything to stop
that.
Jane and Van Pelt are looking
into Tony Redgrave.
And what reason would he have
for murdering Theissens?
We don't know. It could just be
Acosta trying to throw us off.
But Redgrave
does have priors.
What for?
[cell phone rings]
Providing drugs
and alcohol to minors.
um, you, uh, you definitely have
your work cut out for you...
so I will leave you to it.
Excellent.
This is Wainright.
Hey. I just want to acknowledge
receipt of the Red John files.
Thank you for that.
Sure. Yeah.
Anything I can do to help.
Listen, I am assuming
we're on the same page
but you didn't tell your people
about this, did you?
No. I saw no need.
'I agree. Thanks.'
[knocks on door]
Baris Acar?
Ah. Yes, ma'am.
Susan Darcy, FBI.
Uh, did I do
something wrong?
No, it's nothing like that.
I've never been interviewed
by the FBI before.
Mr. Acar, this is
your signature, isn't it?
Yes, ma'am, it is.
And this is a form telling me
that Patrick Jane
brought a visitor here to see
the body of Timothy Carter.
Mr. Jane shot and killed him
in a mall food court.
Do you remember that visit?
Uh, I sure do.
Can you tell me about it?
Well, it stuck in my head
because it was kind of weird.
Weird? What do you mean?
She was blind.
That's kind of weird, right?
Mr. Jane's guest
was a blind woman?
I couldn't figure out
why he brought her.
I mean, she was blind.
Thank you, Mr. Acar.
That's all.
Oh, Mr. Acar
you do know not to speak
to anyone about this?
Whatever you say, ma'am.
Uh, excuse me.
Is that, uh, Tony Redgrave?
Sasha, Sasha, Sasha..
I'm an artist, yeah?
Not a fishmonger.
God sakes, relax.
How am I supposed to relax?
Tony, you're so bloody selfish.
Wyck is dead. He's dead.
Circle of life, babe,
circle of life.
Alright.
Let's try a couple more.
That sullen, grieving look...
I like it.
You Tony?
I'm agent Van Pelt.
This is Patrick Jane
from the California Bureau
of Investigation.
Oh, my God. I love you.
Take your clothes off.
Both of you.
I'm just kidding.
look at your face.
We're here about Wyck Theissens.
It's really sad, right?
Really sad.
I was about to shoot
his comeback campaign.
What a huge bummer that was.
Stabbed to death, right?
What with? A knife? Razor?
Shut up! Tony, God!
We were like family.
We came up together,
me and Wyck.
I walked in every single one
of his shows.
[clicks]
Yes!
That's it, Sasha.
Now you're killing it.
Where were you last night,
Mr. Redgrave?
Oh, uh..
Let's see..
I was... downstairs..
at the pool for a little bit.
Then some drinks at the bar
then dinner,
then we came up here.
Who's "we"?
I don't know. Everyone.
You came up here for a bit,
didn't you, darling?
Yes, you were.
Chin up.
It's quite the act, this, uh,
wide-eyed man-child bit.
Nobody ever calls you
on it, do they?
I'm just really lucky,
you know?
It's just about living
in the moment. Having some fun.
Ah, yes. The joys
of living in the moment.
All fun and games
till someone gets hurt.
How old are these kids?
Everyone in here's an adult.
They're here
because they wanna be.
Nobody's making anyone do
anything they don't wanna do.
- You got it?
- Loud and clear.
Did you make sure
Theissens got it, too?
Don't think you're gonna
put anything on me.
I didn't do
anything to Wyck.
You get to do
whatever you want
'cause no one cares enough
to challenge it.
But Theissens--
he didn't approve, did he?
If he thought you were messing
with those kids of his
he'd have happily
sent you to jail.
You've got it
so twisted, man.
Wyck was refusing to do
anything with any of us.
That's what I heard.
But Duval said
it wasn't a problem.
He said he'd fix it.
Don't leave town without talking
to us first, okay?
I could see Redgrave
murdering Theissens
if he was afraid
to go to jail.
Jane went to talk to Theissens'
assistants again.
Maybe they'll give us something.
Then again, if what
Redgrave says is true
Duval could be our killer.
Stay there. Watch the lobby.
Will do.
Any sign of Mr. Liu?
A GPS on Liu's phone points
to a warehouse in Oakland.
Cho and Rigsby
are checking it out now.
Okay.
Yeah. I'll call you later.
Okay. Me, too.
Sorry. Sarah.
According to GPS,
he's in there.
Okay. Let's go.
Everything okay?
Yeah.
I mean, it's complicated.
Sarah's pregnant.
Oh.
Congratulations.
Thanks.
It's exciting, right?
Yeah. I'm excited.
[clatter]
[Cho]
'Mr. Liu!
This is the CBI!'
Nobody move!
Hands where we can see 'em.
[coughs]
[panting]
There--there's no problem
here, sirs.
We're all friends.
[panting]
[coughs]
'No problem.'
You can go. No problem.
[laughs]
No problem.
Yes? Can I help you?
Rosalind Harker?
Yes. Who is it?
I'm Susan Darcy.
I'm with the FBI.
May I come in?
Sure.
Miss Harker,
you recently paid a visit
to the Sacramento County
Morgue.
Yes.
Did I do something wrong?
That's--
No, it was nothing like that
I just was wondering what
the purpose of your visit was.
Oh.
Well, Patrick Jane wanted me to
check if a man who was in there
was my friend,
Roy Taglioferro.
Roy Taglioferro,
also known as Red John?
Mm. Well..
that's what I've been told
by the authorities, yes.
I suppose it must be true
but I... still
can't quite believe it.
I understand.
So was it Taglioferro
in the morgue?
No. It wasn't Roy.
Well, thank you.
I appreciate your time.
No, please, don't get up.
I'll see myself out.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
What's your connection
to Liu?
What went down
at the warehouse?
No English.
Lawyer.
They can lawyer up
all they want.
All we need
is for you to testify.
Dream on, lady.
I testify to nothing.
You don't know these guys.
So tell me about them.
I import and export
to China, understand?
I deal in electronics,
fashion, luxury goods.
In my business, there are always
gangsters who need paying off.
Shanghai, Guangzhou, Macau--
everywhere the same.
What are they doing here?
I told 'em I had no more
high-fashion copies for them.
They came to change my mind.
So you think they went
to Theissens first
- to send a message to you?
- Maybe.
If so, forget about it.
You can't touch them.
- Really?
- Really.
Like MC Hammer.
Yeah, we hung out with Redgrave.
Dude knows how to party.
Theissens didn't like him
much, though, did he?
Wyck? Wyck hated Redgrave.
He represented everything that
was wrong in the fashion world,
in Wyck's opinion.
And he wouldn't have wanted you
to spend time with Redgrave,
then?
[chuckles]
Are you kidding?
He would have freaked.
He was real protective of us.
But come on. You gotta
cut loose sometimes.
Hmm. I take it you three
are still planning
to put the show on anyway?
Yeah. We wanna do it
for Wyck.
He gave us a chance.
He taught us everything
we needed to know
and we are gonna prove
to the world what he could do.
Yeah, he treated us
with love and respect.
We wanna honor him
the same way.
Mm.
Well, I particularly like this,
uh... gold feathery number.
It's just so, uh...
Well, it's an event.
Uh, where'd you get
all these gold feathers?
We dyed them.
Combination of henna
and iron oxide or something.
Tristan was gonna model it
and Wyck was gonna
close the show with it.
Do you have any more
of those feathers?
I guess so... if you want.
Why the long faces?
You see those two over there
talking to Wainright?
The one with the red tie
looks like state department.
He is.
The other one's from
the Chinese embassy.
Apparently the three
that were intimidating Liu
have diplomatic immunity.
Wainright's cutting 'em loose.
Well, I'd best go
talk to them right away.
Agent Darcy. Hi.
I need to talk
to you, please. May I ?
[both]
Of course.
Is there somewhere
we can talk?
I just need to do one thing.
Where are those gangsters?
In the interrogation room
with their lawyer.
- Come on.
- Thanks.
This won't take a minute.
What was that all about?
-Just trying to solve a murder.
- Tea?
- No, thank you.
I just have
a couple of questions
I need you to clarify for me.
Oh. Fire away.
[water running]
Rosalind Harker.
You met her a couple of
years ago
when you were
tracking Red John?
Uh, yes.
That's correct.
Why do you ask?
She was the lover of a man--
Roy Taglioferro?
Right. Who was really
Red John?
Yes.
But you took Rosalind
to the morgue
to look at the body
of Timothy Carter--
Timothy Carter, who you killed
because hewas Red John.
Yes.
Rosalind told you
that Timothy Carter
wasn't Taglioferro,
didn't she?
Yes. I was hoping
for confirmation from her.
She's hardly
a rock-solid witness.
It had been many years
since her last contact
with Mr. Taglioferro.
She's kind of a lonely soul.
I think she'd rather believe
he was still out there
alive somewhere.
Hmm.
I suppose you're right.
It was Red John
that I killed.
I sure hope so.
Thanks, Patrick.
Pleasure.
I checked out the Chinese thugs.
They're clean.
Let's go to the hotel,
shall we?
Uh, aside from the kids
helping Theissens
only the killer
knows what this is.
I'll tell Rigsby and Van Pelt.
Tell me what happened
with Darcy.
I know it was something.
Well, it's nothing important.
It's bad news.
You've got a bad news expression
on your face.
Darcy talked
to Rosalind Harker.
She knows Timothy Carter
wasn't Red John.
Well, she might suspect,
but she doesn't know.
And you're not
gonna tell her?
Well, of course not.
Why stir up trouble?
Hmm?
Let's go.
Hey, we're headed over
to the hotel.
You on top
of everything here?
Hmm?
Oh, yeah.
Sure.
Wayne?
You're reading a baby book.
Um, yeah, I am.
Um, why?
I...
Yes.
I'm pregnant.
Sarah's pregnant.
- I'm having a baby.
- Oh, my god.
Yikes.
I mean...
Sorry.
It surprised me.
Congratulations.
No, it was a surprise
to me, too.
Still is, actually.
Hard even for me
to believe sometimes.
Are you okay?
Yeah. Oh, I'm--
babies are good, right?
Always wanted to have kids.
Just a little earlier
than I expected.
So are you and Sarah
getting married?
Oh, no. No.
Nothing like that.
Don't wanna rush
into anything, right?
Haven't even been dating
that long.
If... you need anything,
you can ask.
You know that, right?
Yeah.
You should get going, though.
Uh, Wayne..
The kid's lucky.
You're gonna make a great dad.
Yeah? You think?
Yeah. I know it.
Bye.
Thanks.
[indistinct conversations]
Mr. Duval. Hi.
We just need to clear
a few things up.
This is approaching harassment.
We have spoken
to our lawyers.
- Come with me, please.
- Why?
I have a question
I'd like to ask you.
What kind of question?
It's the kind of question
that could clear your name
or prove your guilt.
But, uh, first of all
I'd like you to
empty your pockets, please.
This is ridiculous.
Please.
[sighs]
what is this?
What does it look like?
Well, it's obviously a feather.
It's not mine.
Where did this come from?
Lisbon,
our work here is done.
Thank you for your time,
Mr. Duval. Mrs. Duval.
[both speaking French]
- Hey, Junior.
- Hey. What's up?
How's your investigation going?
Well, that's why we're here.
I found the killer.
- Really?
- Mm-hmm.
Well, who is it?
What happened?
The clue was right
in front of my eyes.
It's all here
in this magazine.
Whoa.
That's... pretty cool.
Is it yours?
Hmm.
Hey, what article
am I supposed to be reading?
Thank you for your time,
Mr. Acosta. We'll stay in touch.
Yes. I love that.
[knock on door]
Don't move a muscle.
Yes?
Hello.
Hi. I'm agent Teresa Lisbon.
You've already met
Patrick Jane, right?
- Hey.
- Hi.
What do you want?
You come to hassle me
about Wyck Theissens' death
some more, have you?
Not really. One or two more
things falling into place
and the killer
shall be revealed.
[knock on door]
I'll get it.
So why have you come here?
I need your help.
hey. I didn't order
room service.
Where did that come from?
Oh, all I know
is that I'm starving.
Do you think I could, uh,
have something from here?
What the hell is that?
It means nothing to you?
Why would it?
You.
Ma'am!
Ma'am! Stop!
I got her.
You're under arrest.
You're losing your touch.
You didn't know it was her.
Don't be ridiculous.
The trick worked
exactly as I intended.
It didn't matter which one
I thought it was.
That's how
a good trick works.
You wouldsay that,
wouldn't you?
[clicks]
We've got your fingerprints
on the murder weapon, Sasha.
It's a perfect match.
Tell me what happened.
It was supposed to be me.
I was supposed to be the face
of Wyck's return.
Because you had been
his inspiration before?
That's right.
I was his muse.
So you went to talk to him
that night?
Mm-hmm.
He was nice, but distant.
I wanted to see the clothes
and he didn't want
to show me them.
I should've known then.
'I told him
they were all beautiful.'
'But there was
this golden feather dress'
'that just hooked me.'
'And that's when he told me.'
'He told me he had found
someone new and fresh.'
'Some little bitch
named Tristan.'
'He told me I was too old.'
'You must have felt
angry, betrayed, even.'
'How could he think he could
treat me like that?'
'So I wanted
to make him suffer.'
'I wanted to make him
eat those words.'
So am I gonna be
outta here soon?
I have a show
in a couple hours
and I need to get there early
for makeup and fitting.
No.
You're not going
to be in the show.
No more shows.
[cell phone rings]
Hello? This is Patrick.
[Rosalind]
'This is Rosalind Harker.
Roy came to see me.'
Is he still there, Rosalind?
'Yes, Roy's here.'
Like I thought, it's all
a big misunderstanding.
He says to tell you
and that Darcy woman
he's going
to clear it all up.
Okay.
Uh, and you're at home?
[laughs]
Where else would I be?
And you're okay?
Of course I am.
Okay. I-I'm on my way.
I want teams around back.
Set up a perimeter.
Nobody in or out.
[piano music]
Rosalind. Where's Roy?
Roy couldn't stay.
Jane
[music continues]
It's the morgue attendant.
You still gonna try
and tell me Red John is dead?
[music continues]